Back

* All about credit reports

* What to look for
    
* Protect your identity

* Contact us

 menu 

  **Free weekly online credit reports are available from Equifax, Experian and TransUnion. Credit reports play an important role in your financial life and we encourage you to regularly check your credit history.** [Request your free credit reports](https://www.annualcreditreport.com/requestReport/landingPage.action)

Contact us
----------

Contact Us

About this site
===============

Website Privacy Policy
----------------------

Central Source LLC is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this website, and we want you to understand our privacy practices in connection with this website.

This Central Source Privacy Policy describes (i) the type of information that we collect and use when you visit our website at www.annualcreditreport.com , and (ii) the steps we take to safeguard your information. This Privacy Policy also describes (a) the parties to which we disclose the information we collect when you use our website, (b) your choices and control over your information, and (c) our practices regarding how we make changes to the Privacy Policy.

We use commercially reasonable physical and electronic systems that are designed to help safeguard your information.

### Details about Our Privacy Policy

### The information we collect about you

Our online privacy policy applies only to your use of this website and to all information you submit to us online during your transaction. Further, we also may get information from you if you send us emails or contact us by phone or letter. Other than in the situations described below, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from or about you while you are using this website.

Specifically, we get information from you when you ask for a free credit report or other services provided through this website. We collect the following information from you online so we can process your requests:

* First and last name (middle initial and suffix, as applicable)
* Social Security Number
* Date of birth
* Current and former mailing address
* Other information we may need to process your request

In addition, the computer that hosts this site automatically collects web log information every time you visit the website. This information includes the date and time you visited our website, the pages you visited and the type of browser you are using. It does not collect information that may identify you as an individual. (See the section entitled ["Cookies and other Technologies"](#cookies) below for more information.)

Each nationwide credit reporting company from whom you request your free credit report may ask for additional information to authenticate your identity or process your request. The credit reporting companies do not share that information with us or with each other. Further, please review the respective privacy policies of the nationwide credit reporting company(ies) when you leave this website.

### How we use your information

We use the information we collect about you to initiate the process for your free credit reports or other services you request. To do this, we give the information to each nationwide consumer credit reporting company you select to provide the free credit report or other service. We also use general information about how visitors use the site to monitor, maintain, and improve this website and other services needed to fulfill your request. (See the section entitled ["Cookies and other Technologies"](#cookies) below for more information.)

We may also use any information that is collected on this site as needed to help manage our everyday business needs, such as audits, reporting and legal compliance.

### Automatically-collected information

Our website uses technologies to collect summary information about how well our site works, what visitors normally click on, what browsers and platforms site visitors use, and the average connection speeds visitors use to connect to the site. Our website may also utilize device identification technologies to assist in detecting and preventing fraud. We use this information to improve the site and to detect and prevent fraudulent activity.

In most cases, these technologies do not collect or use personally identifiable information, such as names or address, and do not associate any online actions with a specific identifiable person. However, in the event we detect fraudulent, suspicious or malicious activity, we will disclose all such information to law enforcement and other third parties as may be needed to enforce our rights, protect our assets and protect the privacy and safety of others. (See also the section entitled ["Who we share information with"](#sharingInfo)).

### Who we share information with

We may share any of the information collected from or about you, as described above, with any of the three nationwide consumer credit reporting companies.

We may also disclose any of the information we collect to companies related to one of the three nationwide consumer credit reporting companies through common ownership or control.

We may also disclose the information to one of the companies that we hire to help us collect and maintain your information, for example, our website hosting providers.

Other companies may get access to your information because they help us process your requests for free credit reports or other services, for example, the company that hosts this website.

We require each third party receiving this information to abide by the restrictions in this privacy policy and not use or disclose the information for any purpose other than as described in this policy. We also require third parties to receive and use the information in compliance with the Fair Credit Reporting Act, Fair and Accurate Credit Transaction Act of 2003, Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and other federal or state regulatory and legal requirements.

We may disclose any of the information collected in response to a valid legal process, such as a lawfully issued subpoena, search warrant, regulatory investigation or inquiry, or court order.

### How we help safeguard your information

When you ask for free credit reports online, programs encrypt the information you provide on the request form before sending it to the nationwide consumer credit reporting company or companies you select. After the credit reporting company gets the information, it decrypts it. We always operate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard your personally identifiable information. This site's security protocols and measures protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access or alteration. These measures include internal and external firewalls, physical security and technological security measures, and encryption of certain information.

Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect the information we maintain, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of the information you transmit to us or that we collect, retain or share.

### Privacy policies of sites we link to

We try to make sure that the websites we link to will treat your personal information responsibly.

However, we cannot control the privacy practices or content of the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies, or other linked sites listed on AnnualCreditReport.com web pages. The owners of these linked sites are responsible for them and you should read their privacy policies in order to better understand what information they collect about you and how they use it.

### Cookies and other technologies

#### What is a cookie?

A cookie is a piece of information that a web server may transfer to your web browser when you visit this website. Cookies are commonly used by websites to improve your experience and to let computer systems recognize your browser. Only the information that you provide, or the choices you make while visiting a website, can be stored in a cookie. For example, the site cannot get your email unless you choose to type it. Allowing a website to create a cookie does not give that or any other site access to the rest of your computer, and only the site that created the cookie can interpret it.

For more information about cookies and how to adjust your settings to choose your cookie preferences, visit your browser's help section.

#### Can I refuse to allow cookies?

You must allow cookies if you want to get credit reports from the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies through this website. If you do not wish to allow cookies, click [getting reports](https://www.annualcreditreport.com/gettingReports.action) for alternative methods for requesting your credit report.

#### How we use cookies on this website

This website uses cookies to:

* Allow you to ask for a free credit report from more than one nationwide consumer credit reporting company during a visit without re-entering your information more than once
* Allow us to gather collective statistical data to help us manage and develop this website
* Help improve how you navigate this website

The cookies on this site collect information only while you are on the site, not after you leave it to go to other sites on the Internet. No one else can read the data our cookies collect unless you give them permission to read them. We may sometimes use other companies to set cookies on this website and collect cookie information for us. We use the cookie information collected by these companies in the same way we discuss above. Those companies may not use these cookies for their own internal purposes or share the information collected with any party except us and the three nationwide consumer credit reporting companies and their contractors.

### Flash Cookies and how you can manage them

We may use Flash Cookies (also known as Local Stored Objects) and similar technologies to personalize and enhance your online experience or for security purposes. Flash Cookies are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your web browser. To manage Flash cookies, please see Adobe's website at http://kb2.adobe.com/cps/526/52697ee8.html or visit www.adobe.com. We do not use Flash cookies or similar technologies for behavioral targeted purposes or to serve interest-based advertising.

### Third Party Advertisers, Interest-Based Ads and Do Not Track Signals

We do not engage third party advertising companies to deliver interest-based advertisements for us. We may allow other third parties, such as entities that assist with security and reporting, to place cookies on your computer when you visit our website. These companies do not collect personal information in this process, and we do not give any personal information to them as part of this process. However, this Privacy Statement does not cover the collection methods or use of the information collected by these companies.

Our websites do not have a mechanism to recognize the various web browser Do Not Track signals because we do not engage in tracking consumers across websites. We do not deliver personalized or interest-based ad.

### Children's privacy

This website is not meant to be used by children under 13. We comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from children under 13.

If you need a credit report for a child under 13, you must request it by mail. We will ask for more information to make sure your request is valid.

### Non-United States Users

If you use this website from outside the United States, please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of this website may be processed and transferred to the United States and be subject to the laws of the United States. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to such laws in your country of residence. By using our website, using any of our website's functions or features, or by providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information in and to the United States.

### This privacy policy does not apply if you are using this site for commercial purposes

This online privacy policy applies when you use the free credit report for personal, family or household purposes. Certain practices described and rights provided may not apply if you use the products or services for commercial purposes.

### Keeping up-to-date on our privacy policy changes

Central Source wants you to be fully informed about how it will protect your privacy. Central Source may change its privacy policy from time to time, but it will not change its practices until they have been posted at this website. If changes occur, the date of revision will also be shown. If we make any material changes to the way we collect, use or disclose your previously-collected information, we will also notify you of those changes via this website.

### How to contact us with questions or comments

If you have questions or comments about Central Source's online privacy notice or our handling of your personal information, please write to:

* Central Source LLC  
    P.O. Box 105283  
    Atlanta, GA 30348-5283

If you have specific questions about your credit file, you should contact the nationwide consumer credit reporting company directly using the contact information provided with your credit report.

You can also find contact information for the nationwide consumer credit reporting companies [requesting reports in special situations](https://www.annualcreditreport.com/requestingReportsInSpecialSituations.action#craContact).

Last Updated: 8/17/2016

Copyright © 2024 Central Source, LLC

Secure Transaction: For your protection, this website is secured with the highest level of SSL Certificate encryption.
